{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Shrek.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Shrek?",
      "answers": ["Ogre", "Knight", "Prince"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Fiona?",
      "answers": ["Princess", "Witch", "Fairy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Donkey?",
      "answers": ["Friend", "Villain", "Prince"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Lord Farquaad?",
      "answers": ["Ruler", "Ogre", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Duloc?",
      "answers": ["City", "Swamp", "Castle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Dragon?",
      "answers": ["Donkey's", "Shrek's", "Fiona's"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Puss?",
      "answers": ["Cat", "Dog", "Rat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Shrek's home?",
      "answers": ["Swamp", "Castle", "Village"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Gingy?",
      "answers": ["Cookie", "Ogre", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Fiona's secret?",
      "answers": ["Ogre", "Fairy", "Witch"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is King Harold?",
      "answers": ["Fiona's", "Shrek's", "Donkey's"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Queen Lillian?",
      "answers": ["Fiona's", "Shrek's", "Donkey's"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Far Far Away?",
      "answers": ["Kingdom", "Swamp", "Castle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Fairy Godmother?",
      "answers": ["Villain", "Hero", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Prince Charming?",
      "answers": ["Villain", "Hero", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Muffin Man?",
      "answers": ["Baker", "Knight", "Ogre"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Artie?",
      "answers": ["King", "Ogre", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Merlin?",
      "answers": ["Wizard", "Knight", "Ogre"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rumpelstiltskin?",
      "answers": ["Villain", "Hero", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Shrek Forever After?",
      "answers": ["Movie", "Book", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
